Kristian Dimitrov

Software Engineer

Puckeridge, Ware, Hertfordshire, United Kingdom

+44 07305558579 <u>kkddimitrov@gmail.com</u> <u>linkedin.com/in/kristian-k-dimitrov/</u> <u>github.com/KristianKKD/</u>

EDUCATION

University of Exeter Advanced Computer Science

Master of Science (M.Sc.)

Oct 2023 – Oct 2024 Simulations and Artificial Intelligence

Middlesex University Games Design

Bachelor of Science (B.Sc.)
Oct 2019 – Jun 2022
Game Design, Development,
and Management

SKILLS

Technologies

Prior experience Rust Java | JavaScript REST | Azure

LANGUAGES

English | Native Bulgarian | Limited

CAREER

Outlier | Al Software Developer

Nov 2024 - Current

Python/C++ developer for refining Al-generated code to meet ideal response quality and accuracy standards.

- Refactoring and optimization of code for clarity, robustness, and reliability.
- Careful inspection for addressing edge cases within responses.
- Development of automated testing for ensured accuracy of solutions.
- Fine-tuning to improve adherence to standard coding practices and expectations.

Silent Sentinel | Software Engineer

May 2022 - Dec 2023

C++ developer and software-side manager for the development of military-grade camera systems, designing solutions for requirements set by customers. We developed on a set of communicating ARM boards with a multi-threaded micro-service architecture approach.

- Low-latency motor control driver, optimized for precision and reliability.
- TCP/IP communications service for message filtering, logging, and routing.
- Scripting service and language for customer procedure programming.
- Directly interacted with customers for requirements and troubleshooting.
- Managed deadlines, designed new features, and delegated tasks for the team.

Silent Sentinel | Production Engineer

Jun 2020 - May 2022

C#/C++ developer with a focus on designing versatile, customizable tools for customers and automated product testing and setup solutions for production.

- Utility to remotely control and view cameras via TCP/IP, featuring custom scripting support, extensive customizability, and comprehensive documentation.
- Email bot to automate proprietary license distribution via external API with integrated customer support interactions.
- Various smaller tools to accelerate development, setup, and the testing process for new products, including software for Honeywell.
- Engineered a circuit for voltage testing on the production line, reducing errors to safeguard sensitive hardware.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Middlesex University | President of Esports Society

Oct 2021 - Jun 2022

Arranged, managed, and maintained several teams, comprising of over 50 people, where I organized participation in tournaments and events for multiple competitive games.

Watford Borough Council | Office Assistant Work Experience

Mar 2016 - Jun 2016

Assisted with general tasks, including physical file management, data entry, spellchecking, website UI redesign suggestions, and other basic tasks.

ABOUT ME

Motivated and creative, I pride myself as being an exceptionally fast learner and flexible jack-of-all-trades. With approaching fifteen years of programming, I specialize in robotics, games, and neural AI but also have deep interests in new technologies and physics. I'm constantly looking for new challenges and opportunities to broaden my skill-sets.

My dream is to be able to interact with a simulated universe, populated with beings that have their own goals and aspirations, unrestricted by the laws of our physics.